https://www.advisoryworld.com/privacy-policy/

Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy and security are of the utmost importance to AdvisoryWorld, and we are committed to safeguarding any information that you share with us.
Contact Us
AdvisoryWorld is a wholly owned subsidiary of LPL Financial LLC.
In order to provide our Applications and services, we must obtain certain personal information from you regarding your accounts and financial relationships. Our pledge is to keep this information secure and to use it only as you so authorize. AdvisoryWorld does not gather any personal information if you are merely visiting our Web site.
You can visit our site, read about our products and services without having to volunteer any information about yourself. We recognize that the personally identifying information that you enter in the Application (whether your own or that of your clients) is very sensitive, and protecting the privacy of this information is a top priority for us. Any personally identifying information that you enter in the Application is kept strictly confidential and not voluntarily shared with any third parties.
AdvisoryWorld only requests you and your clients’ personal and financial information at the time that you use our aggregation, import and new account processing services, in which case you will be asked to provide the following: Investor-related data such as social security number and account number(s). We collect only such information as you knowingly provide to us or specifically authorize us to obtain on your behalf. AdvisoryWorld’s technology allows you to aggregate financial information from various Financial Planning, Portfolio Management, Account Aggregation and CRM applications. In order to provide such services, it is necessary for AdvisoryWorld to access your data from these partners on your behalf. To enable this access, you will need to provide us with all such information that is required by these partners, such as login info from their applications, client tax IDs and Account Numbers. We will use this information only on your behalf, to access your third party accounts and to carry out your instructions.
AdvisoryWorld stores your personal information on secure servers based in the United States of America. AdvisoryWorld does not sell any personally identifiable financial or otherwise information, or account login information to any (i.e. non-affiliate of AdvisoryWorld) third party. Aggregate or Anonymous Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties. For example, we may disclose the number of users that hold a certain investment. We may also disclose anonymized information about your use on AdvisoryWorld, for example if you analyze a certain investment in connection with AdvisoryWorld, we may publicly disclose information about the analysis without providing identifying information about you or otherwise disclosing your participation in the analysis.
AdvisoryWorld reserves the right to disclose or report personally identifiable information as permitted by law (for example, if AdvisoryWorld has a “good faith belief” that it is required to do so in order to (i) comply with applicable law or with legal process (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of AdvisoryWorld; (iii) enforce the terms of this Policy or AdvisoryWorld’s Terms of Use, etc). AdvisoryWorld-authorized employees, customer service representatives and third party sub-contractors will access your personal and financial information only when necessary to comply with your requests, maintain your accounts, or otherwise meet your needs.
To keep your information secure, we require that all of our employees and sub-contractors sign strict confidentiality agreements. Any employee found to have violated this policy may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment. Access to sensitive customer information such as Social Security Numbers and Account Numbers, is highly restricted and is limited to only authorized employees. AdvisoryWorld does not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. For example, information may be accessed by, as permitted by law, non-affiliated companies that work for us in providing development, hosting and security services.
AdvisoryWorld logs IP addresses and browser types. We use these IP addresses to analyze trends and administer the Application. Cookies are used for the same reasons. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer’s hard drive for recordkeeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web Applications use them to provide useful features for their visitors. Cookies allow us to provide you with helpful training and usage capabilities.
AdvisoryWorld does not separately identify, or collect, any information that is specific to children.
By using AdvisoryWorld’s Applications, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information and any related information in the manner and for the purpose described in this Privacy Policy.
AdvisoryWorld’s systems are not currently configured to handle ‘do not track’ requests. AdvisoryWorld reserves the right to change this policy at any time by distributing and/or posting a new privacy policy without notice. We encourage you to review our privacy policy on a regular basis so that You will be aware of any changes to it.
The information and materials contained in these pages are subject to change. You can review this policy and any updates at any time by browsing to our website then clicking on Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of AdvisoryWorld and this service, or your dealings with this Web site, you can email us at: info@advisoryworld.com.
CA Consumer Privacy Portal – Exercise Your Rights: https://privacy.lpl.com
Welcome aboard
Please provide your information and receive a Free Trial of AdvisoryWorld
Once your information is submitted, you may access a full working version for a 14 -day period.
I am a*
---Rep RIARep Broker/DealerRep WirehouseRep BankRep Insurance CompanyHome Office RIAHome Office Broker/DealerHome Office WirehouseHome Office BankHome Office Insurance CompanyHome Office TAMPTechnology ProviderIndividual Investor
Product Interest
Investment Analytics
Portfolio Modeling
Proposal Generation
Digital On-Boarding
Model Fact Sheet Generation
Preferred Delivery Methods
Web-Applications
API
Professional Services
How did you find us?
Google or other Web-search
Word of Mouth
Trade Publication
Trade Show
Email Received
Here to help
Thank you for your Free Trial request. We will contact you shortly with credentials.
Welcome
Login For Registered User
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua.
Forgot password?
Keep me logged in
By logging in, you agree to Advisoryworld’s
Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
Log in
Not a mamber? Join Now
WelcomeRegistered User LoginPlease click on one of the following buttons to login to your application of choice. If you have any issues with login, please contact support.
Advisor Proposal GeneratorSCANalyticsIntelligenceICE
Loading
Here to help
Contact Us
Once your information is submitted, we will contact you in short order. Please feel free to dial us on 800-480-3888 with any urgent requests.
I am a*
---Rep RIARep Broker/DealerRep WirehouseRep BankRep Insurance CompanyHome Office RIAHome Office Broker/DealerHome Office WirehouseHome Office BankHome Office Insurance CompanyHome Office TAMPIndividual Investor
Product Interest
Investment Analytics
Portfolio Modeling
Proposal Generation
Digital On-Boarding
Model Fact Sheet Generation
Preferred Delivery Methods
Web-Applications
How did you find us?
Thank you for your submission. We will be in touch shortly. Please dial us on 800-480-3888 with any urgent matters.
Here to help
Contact Support
Once your information is submitted, our support team will contact you as soon as possible. If this is an urgent issue please dial 800-480-3888
Product*
---SCANalyticsAdvisor Proposal GeneratorModel Document BuilderIntelligenceReports on DemandICEPower OptimizerRAMCAPAPIOther
Here to help
Thank you for your submission. We will contact you soon to service your request. Please dial us on 800-480-3888 with any urgent matters.
Loading
